webtender.com 2015-05-20

# The Webtender: Privacy Policy

The Webtender is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. The following discloses how information is collected and used for The Webtender web site. In general it states that, except in the case where you explicitly give permission to provide your contact information to a third party, any personal information you provide on this site will be only be known to yourself and The Webtender.

### General Information

The Webtender does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address, unless you actively provide this by filling out registration forms etc. However, The Webtender does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as your IP address, your browser type and operating system, and the address of the web site that referred you to The Webtender. This information is collected by The Webtender and is used for to provide potential advertisers with statistics, to administer the web site, and to track abusive users. 

Some sections of The Webtender may also use cookies. For more information on how they are used by The Webtender, please click here.

### Polls, surveys and voting

None of these features require you to provide any personal information. Your IP address is stored along with your answer or vote, but is only used to avoid multiple votes from the same person.

### Public Forums

The Webtender makes several forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas will remain become public information available and exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Please note that the chat application is hosted by a third party, and The Webtender has no control over how information in this chat is used.

### Submitting Recipes

Everyone that submit recipes to The Webtender must provide their name and a working e-mail address. This information will be listed on the web site and should be considered public. You may alter this information in the future, but it can only be removed if the recipe(s) you submitted are also removed.

### Feedback and suggestions

To be able to reply to feedback and suggestions you are required to supply an e-mail address. However, this will be treated according to the e-mail policy and never be sold or used in mass mailings.

### Ads served by third party

The Webtender use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

### Opt-Out

The Webtender also gives users the option of changing and modifying information previously provided. For the forums, click on the User profile link to change your personal information.

### Disclaimer

This site contains links to other sites and The Webtender can not be held responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites.

## Additional information

If you have additional questions regarding your privacy on The Webtender, feel free to contact privacy@webtender _._ com, or visit one of the links below.

  * **E-mail policy**
  * **Cookies information**

* * *

**How do I pour? What is 'cl', 'oz' and 'pt'? How should I handle glassware?.**  
Find the answers in The Bartender's Handbook. 

* * *

Home · Search · Forums · Bookstore · Barstore · Web Index · Feedback · Survey

Copyright © 1995-2015 The Webtender.  
About | Disclaimer | Privacy policy
